[Music]
[音乐]
all right hello everyone thanks for
好的，大家好
coming to attend this session I'm Poonam
来参加本次会议的我是Poonam
I work in the JVM sustaining engineering
我从事JVM维持工程
group at Oracle and in this session we
甲骨文小组，在本次会议中，我们
are going to you know talk a bit about
要去你知道谈论一些
the new GC logging for Mac that's coming
Mac即将推出的新GC日志记录
up in Java 9 the mandatories slide that
在Java 9中，强制性规定
I have to include so new GC logging in
我必须包括新的GC登录
Java 9 it's it's a big change massive
Java 9这是一个巨大的巨大变化
change that's coming in Java 9 and
更改Java 9和
actually it follows another major change
实际上，这是另一个重大变化
which is being introduced in JDK 9 which
JDK 9中引入了
is unified JVM logging framework so the
是统一的JVM日志记录框架，因此
GC logging would be using this framework
GC日志记录将使用此框架
new framework in JDK 9 to log its
JDK 9中的新框架来记录其
messages and in this session we are
消息，在本次会议中，我们
going to talk about you know a bit about
谈谈你知道一点
unified JVM framework GC logging the new
统一的JVM框架GC记录新的
command line option that we need to use
我们需要使用的命令行选项
to you know to see equivalent
你知道看到等效
information that we will like to use to
我们将要使用的信息
see with earlier JDK versions with the
参见带有早期JDK版本的
GC logging options here's what I'm going
GC记录选项，这就是我要去的地方
to talk about unified JVM logging
谈论统一的JVM日志记录
framework new in Java 9 how GC code is
Java 9中的新框架GC代码如何
DC logging code is reimplemented to use
DC日志记录代码被重新实现以使用
that framework new command line option -
该框架的新命令行选项-
X log which is actually added by the
X日志实际上是由
framework and GC code has introduced new
框架和GC代码引入了新的
tags to be used along with this command
与该命令一起使用的标签
line option you know and what
行选项，您知道什么
considerations are we need to use with
需要考虑的因素
this command line option to get the
此命令行选项以获取
equivalent information in the GC logs
GC日志中的等效信息
what happens to the old GC logging flags
旧的GC日志记录标志发生了什么
we'll see and then take a look at some
我们先看再看一些
of the examples
的例子
unified jvn logging framework JEP 1:58
统一的jvn日志记录框架JEP 1:58
who was the proposal to add this new
谁是添加此新提案的提案
enhancement to add this new framework
增强功能以​​添加此新框架
into JDK 9 it adds a new command-line
到JDK 9中，它添加了一个新的命令行
option minus X log and with this there
选项减去X日志，并在那里
are you know some tags added up into
你知道一些标签加进去吗
various parts of the JVM you know
您知道的JVM的各个部分
representing different parts of the JVM
代表JVM的不同部分
that can be used along with this command
可以与此命令一起使用
line option to fine tune the information
行选项可微调信息
we want to see in the in the logging for
我们想在日志中看到
example GC class JFR modules etc and
示例GC类JFR模块等，以及
these logging messages coming from the
这些日志消息来自
framework you know whichever all the
您知道的所有框架
systems using this framework of we can
使用该框架的系统，我们可以
use tags to categorize these logging
使用标签对这些日志进行分类
messages it's possible to use a
消息，可以使用
combination of tags with minus X log you
标记与减号X的组合会记录您
know a set of combinations of tags to
知道一组标签组合
really select the messages which we want
真正选择我们想要的消息
to see in our logging and all the logins
以查看我们的日志记录和所有登录信息
can be you know done at different levels
你能知道在不同层次完成吗
there are certain levels defined error
有一定程度的定义错误
warning info debug.trace and develop
警告信息debug.trace和开发
develop is for non product bills the
开发非产品账单
other levels are available in the
其他级别在
product bills and the messages can be
产品帐单和消息可以是
decorated which means that there are
装饰，这意味着有
certain decorators available which can
某些可用的装饰器可以
be used to you know enhance the message
习惯于了解信息
you can add additional information to
您可以将其他信息添加到
the logging message and the the default
日志消息和默认
decorators are uptime level and types
装饰器的正常运行时间级别和类型
but you can of course change the
但您当然可以更改
decorators that you want to see with
您想看到的装饰
your logging messages it's possible to
您的日志消息是可能的
redirect logging to a file so all this
将日志重定向到文件，所以所有这些
is
是
under the unified JVM logging framework
在统一的JVM日志记录框架下
the help option can be used with minus X
help选项可以与减号X一起使用
log and it provides you no information
日志，它没有为您提供任何信息
couple on the complete syntax of the
夫妇的完整语法
command how you can use it what are the
命令如何使用它
options that can be used along with - X
可以与-X一起使用的选项
logs
日志
- the most important thing to note here
-这里要注意的最重要的事情
is the what what which you know is it
你知道的是什么
comes after - X log : what is the
之后-X log：什么是
combination of tags and the levels for
标签和级别的组合
which we want to see information coming
我们希望看到即将到来的信息
from different you know components of
从不同的你知道
the JVM and note the the the star or the
JVM，并注意星号或
asterisks which follows d tag sets it
d标签后面的星号将其设置
denotes a wild-card which means that I I
表示通配符，表示II
want to see the logging messages which
想查看日志消息
are associated with these you know super
与这些你知道超级相关
set of the tags that I am specifying on
我在其上指定的标签集
the command along with - X lock command
该命令以及-X锁定命令
so I would like to see messages that are
所以我想看看
tagged with at least these tag sets but
至少使用这些标签集进行了标签，但
they may have you know other types as
他们可能会让您知道其他类型的
well associated with them let's take a
与他们紧密联系，让我们
quick look at the other options that can
快速查看其他可以
be used with the - X log you can change
与-X日志一起使用可以更改
the output you know using the output
使用输出您知道的输出
option whether you want it to be
选择是否要
redirected to STD out all you want to
重定向到STD出所有您想要的
redirect it to a file the decorators
将其重定向到装饰文件
time uptime time malaise so these
时间正常运行时间不适
decorators enhance or add the
装饰器增强或添加
information to the logging messages as I
信息到我的日志消息
said uptime level and tags are by
表示正常运行时间级别和标记
default enabled but you can remove them
默认启用，但您可以将其删除
or change them and the output options
或更改它们以及输出选项
are basically - you know - to enable or
基本上是-您知道-是启用还是
disable the log file rotation or to
禁用日志文件轮换或
specify how many log files you
指定您有多少个日志文件
to be rotated and what is the size of
要旋转的大小是多少
each file log file you would be
您将成为的每个文件日志文件
interested in now unified DC logging so
现在对统一的DC记录感兴趣，因此
with Jeff 271 GC logging has also been
Jeff 271的GC记录功能
read has also been reimplemented to use
阅读也已重新实现以使用
the new framework so GC uses - X log
GC使用的新框架-X日志
command and GC is the main tag to be
命令，GC是要使用的主要标签
used with - X log and there are other
用于-X日志，还有其他
tags as well you know available for fine
您也知道可以使用的标签
tuning the GC logging that we are
调整我们正在使用的GC日志记录
interested in and the old GC logging
对旧的GC记录感兴趣
options might come as a shock will be
选项可能会吓到
removed in JDK 9 so you know we if you
已在JDK 9中删除，所以您知道我们是否
are launch scripts or your command line
是启动脚本还是您的命令行
options are using the old GC logging
选项正在使用旧的GC日志记录
option they will have to be removed when
选项，它们将必须在
you move to using Java 9 8 1 4 5 0 9 -
您开始使用Java 9 8 1 4 5 0 9-
was the bug ID under which you know the
是您知道的错误ID
this enhancement was integrated into the
此增强功能已集成到
repository so if you are interested in
存储库，所以如果您对
looking at specific changes that were
看看当时的具体变化
done for you know de belem ending GC
为您所知de belem结束了GC
logging you can see the changes done
记录您可以看到所做的更改
under this bug
在这个错误下
let's take a look at the example output
让我们看一下示例输出
that you would see with the - X log GC
您将看到-X log GC
so here I am specifying that I want to
所以在这里我指定我想
see messages logs messages that are
查看消息记录以下消息
tagged with GC tag and are logged at a
用GC标签标记并记录在
level trace and and if we specify a
级别跟踪，如果我们指定一个
particular level the messages below that
特定级别以下的消息
level are also you know slots so in this
水平也是你知道插槽，所以在这个
case messages logged with trace debug
用跟踪调试记录的案例消息
info error and warning would get log so
信息错误和警告将获取日志，因此
in the output we can see that all the
在输出中，我们可以看到所有
messages that are tagged with GC are
用GC标记的消息是
printed out
打印出来
the first three columns come from the
前三列来自
logging framework and they are uptime
日志记录框架，它们正常运行
level and tags and the rest of the
级别和标签，其余的
message is coming from the GC code do
消息来自GC代码吗
you see you know code in the JVM what
您会看到您知道JVM中的代码
happens to the old GC logging flags as I
我发生在旧的GC记录标志上
said they will be removed they are
说他们将被删除
actually they have been removed in the
实际上它们已经在
repository but we still retain three
存储库，但我们仍然保留三个
most popular flags up in GC pin GC
GC引脚GC中最受欢迎的标志
details and X log GC they won't be
详细信息和X log GC，它们不会
showing you the old output but they have
向您显示旧的输出，但它们有
been internally mapped to the
在内部映射到
corresponding the X log configuration so
对应于X日志配置，因此
that you know at least for these flags
你至少知道这些标志
you don't have to update your launch
您不必更新您的发布
scripts and the command line options
脚本和命令行选项
they will show the new output but they
他们将显示新的输出，但他们
are still honored you won't get a you
仍然很荣幸你不会得到你
know error message and that the JVM
知道错误消息，并且JVM
itself doesn't launch these flags are
本身不启动这些标志是
deprecated and will be removed in a
已过时，将在
future Java release so all in all 43 GC
未来的Java版本，所以总共有43个GC
logging flags are removed with this
记录标志与此删除
change
更改
here's an example of for GC logging code
这是GC日志记录代码的示例
change that Renton as part of the free
更改伦顿作为免费的一部分
implementation so if you see earlier we
实施，因此，如果您之前看到过，
had underpinned GC details we had GC log
支撑了GC详细信息，我们拥有了GC日志
or TTY and
或TTY和
it invoked function print to send be
它调用了函数print发送来
logging message either to our console or
将消息记录到控制台或
to a logging file it has been replaced
到日志文件已被替换
with log underscore level macro and that
与日志下划线级别宏，那
macro is implemented in the logging
宏在日志记录中实现
framework so this macro what does it do
框架，所以此宏有什么作用
it you know there are different macros
你知道有不同的宏
for for each level and here you are
对于每个级别，在这里
telling that I want to log this message
告诉我要记录此消息
which is heap usage transition details
这是堆使用情况转换的详细信息
at which tag associated with tags GC and
与标签GC和
heap and I want to log this message at
堆，我想将此消息记录在
info level so if someone on the command
信息级别，因此如果有人在命令
line uses X log : GC plus heat is equal
该行使用X log：GC加热量等于
to info or you don't have to say info
信息，或者您不必说信息
because that's the default level then
因为那是默认级别
this message would get printed another
此消息将再次打印
example we used to have a flag pink
例如我们曾经有一个标志粉红色
adaptive size policy so that has been
自适应尺寸政策
removed and a logging message at trace
删除并在跟踪记录消息
level is logged using tags G C and L go
使用标签GC和L go记录液位
and the message remains the same some
和消息保持不变
examples so I have tried to use since
例子，所以我尝试使用
the g1 garbage collector is the default
g1垃圾收集器是默认的
in JDK 9 so my examples are using G 1
在JDK 9中，所以我的示例使用G 1
with JDK 8 and you know the default
使用JDK 8，您知道默认值
collector in JDK 9 so this example using
JDK 9中的收集器，因此此示例使用
the old flag is with the JDK 9 and the
JDK 9和
next slide I will show you the example
下一张幻灯片，我将向您展示示例
of the output with JDK 9 using G 1
使用G 1的JDK 9输出
collector so here we can see this is the
收集器，所以在这里我们可以看到这是
usual output you know with print GC
您使用打印GC知道的常规输出
option to get the equivalent information
获得等效信息的选项
with the new logging framework in Java 9
Java 9中的新日志记录框架
we would be using minus X log colon GC
我们将使用减X对数冒号GC
so print GC if you are using print GC it
因此，如果您正在使用打印GC，请打印GC
will be replaced with the minus X log :
将被替换为减号X log：
GC it gives the same kind of same level
GC它给出相同的相同水平
of information and you know the
信息，你知道
additional information comes from the
其他信息来自
framework that these are the tags and
这些是标签的框架，
this is the time at which this event
这是这个事件的时间
occurred then GC details again with the
发生，然后GC详细信息再次与
g1 collector with JDK 8 this is the
带有JDK 8的g1收集器，这是
information that we used to get within
我们过去获取的信息
GC details in Java 9 we need to use a
Java 9中的GC详细信息，我们需要使用
minus X log : GC star so G's by GC star
减X log：GC星号，所以G由GC星号表示
or asterisk we are saying
或星号
please log messages that include at
请记录以下消息
least GC tag in them and they may have
它们中最少的GC标签，并且它们可能具有
other tags associated with them so if
与他们相关的其他标签，如果
you notice in width in GC details with
您会在GC详细信息中注意到
g1 you are you can see the failed level
g1你是你可以看到失败的水平
information here you know D logging
您在这里了解的信息D日志记录
messages are giving us information about
消息给我们有关的信息
the about the different phases of g1
关于g1的不同相位
garbage collector but with X log : GC
垃圾收集器，但带有X日志：GC
star that information is missing so with
明星，信息丢失，所以
other collectors you would get the same
其他收藏家，你会得到相同的
level of information with the - X log :
-X日志的信息级别：
GC star but with g1
GC星，但带有g1
we need to use GC plus phases is equal
我们需要使用GC加相等于
to debug to get the phases level
调试以获得阶段级别
information because that information is
信息，因为该信息是
logged under GC and phases tiles and
在GC和阶段磁贴下记录和
that's logged at a debug level so as to
记录在调试级别，以便
you know keep the detail level separated
你知道细节水平分开
from GC star and you need to specify
来自GC star，您需要指定
additional tags to get more detailed
其他标签以获取更多详细信息
level information print heap add GC
级别信息打印堆添加GC
which you know using which we can get
你知道用哪个我们可以得到
the heap usage details before or after a
堆使用之前或之后的堆使用详细信息
GC for that in Java 9 we would be using
我们将使用Java 9中的GC
- X log : GC + heap is equal to debug
-X日志：GC +堆等于调试
which means logs you know print the log
这意味着您知道的日志会打印日志
messages tagged with the GC and heap and
标有GC和堆的消息，以及
you know at debug levels being printed
你知道在调试级别打印
at debug levels we have options print GC
在调试级别，我们可以选择打印GC
application concurrent time print GC
应用程序并发时间打印GC
applications stop time in JDK 8 which
应用程序在JDK 8中的停止时间
are used to print the application
用于打印应用程序
runtime and application stop time
运行时和应用程序停止时间
in JDK 9 we would be using - xlab : safe
在JDK 9中，我们将使用-xlab：安全
point so with this tag the application
要点，因此使用此标签
run time and application stop time the
运行时间和应用程序停止时间
same kind of information same level of
相同类型的信息
information would be available with the
信息将与
safe point tag print adaptive size
安全点标签打印适应尺寸
policy which you know prints the heap
您知道的策略会打印堆
sizing and the collection set
大小和收藏集
construction decisions are being made by
正在由施工决策
the collector in Java 9 we use GC + algo
Java 9中的收集器，我们使用GC +算法
star is equal to trace so GC and I'll go
星等于痕迹，所以GC，我去
take a go plus some other tags you know
尝试一下，再加上其他一些您知道的标签
messages at the trace levels continuing
跟踪级别的消息继续
distribution which used to print the the
用于打印
survivor size are the age distribution
幸存者人数是年龄分布
of surviving objects in the survivor
幸存者中幸存物体的数量
spaces so for that option we would be
空格，因此对于该选项，我们将
replacing it with minus X log GC + h is
用负X log GC + h替换它是
equal to trace so it gives the you know
等于跟踪，所以它使您知道
even the text remains the same it gives
甚至文字也一样
the same information so we had minus X
相同的信息，所以我们减去X
log GC option we have we still have
我们拥有的日志GC选项
minus X log GC option up until JDK 9 and
减去X log GC选项，直到JDK 9和
that's used to you know redirect the the
这用于您知道重定向
logging output to a file and we could
将输出记录到文件中，我们可以
use options UGC log file rotation to
使用选项UGC日志文件旋转到
enable the logging file rotation and
启用日志文件旋转和
this is little how those options could
这些选择几乎不可能
be used to enable rotation a file
用于启用旋转文件
logging file rotation and to redirect
记录文件旋转并重定向
the output to a file even though this
即使输出到文件
option would still be there in JDK 9
JDK 9中仍然存在该选项
minus x log GC but the rest of the
减去x log GC，其余的
options will be removed
选项将被删除
and X log VC would be mapped to minus X
和X log VC将映射为减X
log G C you know : file is equal to the
您知道的日志GC：文件等于
name of the file so this is how we can
文件名，所以我们可以这样
redirect the output to a file and we
将输出重定向到文件，我们
could enable file rotation and specify
可以启用文件旋转并指定
the number of files we want and use and
我们想要和使用的文件数以及
what should be the size of each file so
每个文件的大小应该是多少
other useful types to get more you know
其他有用的类型以获得更多您知道的
information and details about minus X
有关减号X的信息和详细信息
log command if we use minus X log : GC
如果使用减X log则执行log命令：GC
star is equal to trace so that prints
星号等于迹线，以便打印
the lowest level of information you know
您知道的最低级别的信息
of GC logging information so trace as we
GC日志记录信息，因此我们可以跟踪
the most detailed level to be specified
指定的最详细的级别
and GC star means include all the GC
和GC星号表示包括所有GC
related options all the GC related tags
相关选项所有与GC相关的标签
in the output so this provides we you
在输出中，这样可以为您提供
know all of GC logging at the lowest
了解最低的所有GC日志记录
level and minus X log all is equal to
水平和负X log全部等于
trace which means I want to see GC logs
跟踪，这意味着我想查看GC日志
from all the subsystems of the JVM at
来自JVM的所有子系统
the lowest level and it is possible to
最低的水平，有可能
disable the logging all together using
一起禁用日志记录
the disable options with minus X log and
带有X日志的禁用选项和
as I said help provides a you know the
正如我所说的，“帮助”提供了
sense in techs and examples for minus X
负号X的技术感和示例感
log command and minus x log logging is
log命令和减x日志记录为
equal to trace actually gives you know
等于跟踪实际上使您知道
enables tracing for the logging
启用日志记录跟踪
framework itself so it provides
框架本身，因此它提供了
information about the available types
有关可用类型的信息
implemented by the system what are the
由系统实现的是什么
available tag sets what are the
可用标签集是什么
available levels and decorators and
可用的级别和装饰器，以及
what's the active configuration of you
您的活动配置是什么
know available taxes is it possible to
知道可用税有可能
dynamically configure minus X log yes it
动态配置减X日志是的
is we can use J command or and beans
我们可以使用J命令还是and bean
- you know dynamically change the
-您知道动态更改
options of minus X log if we use a VM
如果使用VM，则减X日志的选项
dot log with J command a diagnostic
用J命令进行点日志诊断
command it shows you know what are the
命令显示您知道什么是
options that can be used to configure
可用于配置的选项
the the parameters of - X log and for
-X log和的参数
here in this example I am using what is
在此示例中，我使用的是
equal to GC star which means I am
等于GC星，这意味着我是
changing the tags that can be used with
更改可用于的标签
- X log - G C star so I put together
-X日志-GC星号，所以我放在一起
you know these stables mapping the old
你知道这些马s映射着旧的
GC Flags - the new X log configurations
GC标志-新的X日志配置
that can give us the equivalent of GC
可以给我们相当于GC的
logging information which we use to get
记录我们用来获取的信息
with the old Flags so for example print
与旧的标志，例如打印
the g1 print heap regions which is
g1打印堆区域是
available in JDK 8 in JDK 9 we can use X
在JDK 9中的JDK 8中可用，我们可以使用X
logs : GC + region is equal to trace so
日志：GC +区域等于跟踪，因此
you know by looking at the code by
通过查看代码可以知道
running some tests I prepared these
运行一些测试，我准备了这些
tables mapping the old options to the
表将旧选项映射到
new configurations so maybe you know you
新的配置，所以也许你知道你
can refer to these tables later on when
以后可以参考这些表
you are migrating your applications to
您正在将应用程序迁移到
Java 9 and updating your launch scripts
Java 9和更新启动脚本
so with that I come to an end of you
所以我结束了你
know this presentation thank you so much
知道这个演讲非常感谢你
[Applause]
[掌声]
this I will be uploading it somewhere so
这个我会上传到某个地方
this will be publicly available yes I am
这将是公开可用的，是的
not aware of that yeah
不知道是的
yes I I guess that that we did with the
是的，我想我们是用
three popular flag sir but it would have
三个受欢迎的国旗先生，但它会
been you know having so much redundant
你知道很多多余的东西吗
code and maintaining it in the codebase
代码并将其维护在代码库中
would have been difficult so and they
本来很难，所以他们
don't do anything at least JVM bub up
不要做任何事情，至少可以使JVM崩溃
but once that you know let the users
但是一旦知道，就让用户
have garbage in their in their launch
发射时有垃圾
scripts it they would never remove it
脚本，他们将永远不会删除它
you know
你懂
yeah but you know being in being in
是的，但是你知道在
sustaining I have seen that the you
支持我已经看到你
think that lunch the people are not in
认为人们不在午餐
control of their launch scripts if you
控制他们的启动脚本，如果您
take a look at you know some of the
看一下你知道的一些
launch scripts they are full of trash
启动脚本，它们到处都是垃圾
you know people don't know where those
你知道人们不知道那些人在哪里
options are coming from and if this is
选项来自，如果这是
allowed you will have all the junk
允许你拥有所有的垃圾
accumulated in the launch file so that
累积在启动文件中，以便
this will force them to remove it which
这将迫使他们将其删除
is garbage should be removed anywhere in
是否应将垃圾清除到任何地方
future if we duplicate it now and remove
将来，如果我们现在复制它并删除
it in future anyway at some point you
将来无论如何你都会
have to remove it right all right and
必须将其正确删除，
anyway these options we say that these
无论如何，我们说这些
are unsupported and we don't care you
不受支持，我们不在乎您
know we can remove them anytime we want
知道我们可以随时删除它们
and coming back to your question that
回到你的问题
don't do anything just let them be there
什么也不做，只是让他们在那里
if we just let them be there you would
如果我们让他们在那里，你会
expect the output when some failure
遇到一些故障时期待输出
occurs you will say oh I had these
发生你会说哦，我有这些
options on why don't I see my log file
为什么我看不到日志文件的选项
and why don't I see something in my log
为什么我看不到日志
file you won't you know because then why
文件你不会知道，因为那为什么
didn't you tell me that I had to remove
你不是告诉我我必须删除
it nobody reads warnings they are just
没有人读警告，他们只是
you know the processor started you you
你知道处理器启动了你吗
never read what I what is being printed
从不读我正在打印的内容
on the console
在控制台上
decoding change
解码变化
yep
是的
so this is a macro you know we have log
所以这是一个宏，您知道我们有日志
underscore info log and the score trace
下划线信息日志和分数跟踪
these are encapsulated macros and that
这些是封装的宏，
the macro is defined as log underscore
该宏定义为log下划线
level which actually then blows into
然后实际上吹入的水平
these different macros for each level
每个级别都有这些不同的宏
right so so this macro is accepting the
对，所以这个宏正在接受
tags and then it calls a function
标签，然后调用一个函数
passing it you know the specific
通过它，你知道具体的
function for that level and
该级别的功能和
encapsulating this message
封装此消息
yeah yeah so this this macro would
是的，所以这个宏会
actually check you know if this level is
实际检查您是否知道此级别是
enabled or not and then it logs the
启用或未启用，然后记录
message so yes so this macro log
消息，是的，所以此宏日志
underscore trace will actually check so
下划线跟踪实际上将检查
this actually expands to the code and
这实际上扩展为代码，
which is a check
这是一张支票
I don't know right right okay
我不知道对不对
okay yeah okay all right yeah I'll get
好的，好的，好的，我会得到
in touch with you regarding yeah sure
与您联系，是的，肯定的
so yes get ready be prepared to you know
所以是的，准备好要知道
for this new logging format in Java 9
Java 9中这种新的日志记录格式
thank you
谢谢
[Music]
[音乐]